ABHISHEK KUMAR SINGH

IT Specialist, Web Developer and UI UX Designer

Always used to be a Tech Lover from Birth. Having a great interest in Hardware and Networking, I Love to deal with all kinds of Computer Related work and troubleshooting in Windows. Also Have a Brief Knowledge with regards to Front-end Web Development (React, Html, Css).



abhishek123kumar123singh@gmail.com

+91 9778746469

Rourkela, India

linkedin.com/in/abhishek-kumar-singh-1652161bb

B-Tech(CSE) Lovely Professional University

08/2020 - Present

EDUCATION

Phugwara, Punjab

India

India

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Campus Networking system (06/2022 - 09/2022)

Finance Excel Dashboard (09/2022 - 11/2022)

Smart drainage system (06/2019 - 10/2019)

Auto Driving GPS CAR (06/2019 - 12/2019)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Creative Associate (Remote)

Chegg India Private Limited

06/2022 - Present Used to manage and work with the creative of the company

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

IT Specialist Intern (On-site)

Larsen & Toubro

05/2022 - 07/2022 Kansbahal, Odisha, India I was assign with the work of Computer Netorking and troubleshooting of

 CLI commands, Remote troubleshooting, Hardware troubleshooting

Graphics Designer (Remote)

Ricoz India

08/2022 - Present India Used to help with Designing services

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

Web Developer (Remote)

Web Enduring Solution

11/2021 - 01/2022 I used to Make Websites for their company

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Wordpress

LANGUAGES

English Hindi

INTERESTS

Graphics Designing Figma DSA Web Designing Data Handling Java Hardware and Networking Photoshop

SKILLS

Front-End Web Developer	• • • • •
Graphics Editing	• • • • •
DSA	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Hardware and Networking	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Troubleshooting	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

ACHIEVEMENTS

STATE LEVEL SCIENCE EXHIBITION (11/2019)

Awarded 2nd position in state level science competition.

NATIONAL LEVEL DRAWING COMPETITION (2019)

Placed at 4th position is national level drawing competition

STATE LEVEL DRAWING COMPETITION (2018)

Placed at 1st position in state level drawing competition

CERTIFICATES

Google IT Support Professional Certificate (06/2022 - 01/2023)

The Bits and Bytes of the computer networking by google (10/2022 - 01/2023)

Technical support fundamentals from google (03/2022 - 04/2022)

Advance Python Course (12/2020 - 03/2020)